<root>
    <image id="banner">
        <![CDATA[<img src="http://www.tcoz.com/newtcoz/images/banner.png" alt="tcoz tim consolazio banner" width="590" height="56">]]>
    </image>
    <paragraph position='r1c1'>
        <![CDATA[
            Tcoz.com is a digital attic related to my business as an independent software and RIA developer.
            Tcoz Tech Services is my "Doing Business As", and represents the business entity of Tim Consolazio (me).
            You'll find info on my latest projects, a list of services, general thoughts and blurbs on what I'm up to,
            and so on.</br></br>
            Please note that <strong> <a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/180y3Vm0DD4qzXJjPyNRh2zVTp7tDqcIRhIL_64uweEc/edit?hl=en_US" target="_blank">my resume</a></strong>
            may under no circumstances may be altered or edited in any way.</br></br>
            Drop me a line at <a href="mailto:tcoz@tcoz.com"><strong>tcoz@tcoz.com</strong></a> if you have need of a developer with a
            deep knowledge of technologies primarily related to delivery of media and information-focused applications
            on the web (though desktop is within my skill set as well).
        ]]>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph position='r1c2'>
        <![CDATA[
            <strong>Please note:</strong></br></br>
            <ul>
                <li>I don't discuss rates I'm charging clients.</li>
                <li>My rate varies depending on specific responsibilities in a given project (straight dev, management, architecture, etc.), as well as the arrangement (full-time onsite, partial telecommute, full-time offsite). </li>
                <li><strong><a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/180y3Vm0DD4qzXJjPyNRh2zVTp7tDqcIRhIL_64uweEc/edit?hl=en_US" target="_blank">My resume</a></strong> is available in PDF format, and may not be edited or altered in any way. </li>
                <li>I don't offer discounted rates for W2. </li>
                <li>I'm not a professional "data tier" guy, or a graphic designer/"Flash Designer". I'm an architect thinker that likes to code.</li>
                <li>I'm in the NYC area, and can't relocate. </li>
            </ul>
        ]]>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph position="r2c1">
        <![CDATA[
            <ul>
                <li><strong>Advanced OOP</strong> skills in all  programming environments.</li>
                <li><strong>ActionScript:</strong> AS3, RobotLegs, PureMVC, Mate, Flex framework, etc. Many, many years of experience. "Hero" sdk (mobile ActionScript-based apps).</li>
                <li><strong>PHP:</strong> ver. 5+, Zend framework. Several projects.</li>
                <li><strong>Java:</strong> Servlets/JSP, basic Hibernate, BlazeDS, OpenAMF, Objectify (GAE), etc. Java is my primary server-side language. Some Android dev using Java as well.</li>
                <li><strong>Python:</strong> General development skills, particularly on GAE. I use Python more every day. Knowledge of Paramiko, Crypto, PyAMF, BeautifulSoup, etc.</li>
                <li><strong>General Web:</strong> HTML/CSS/JS, some HTML5 (very little is standardized across browsers, but I keep my eye on it), AJAX, JQuery, etc. To me, this is all "utility". </li>
           	</ul>
        ]]>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph position="r2c2">
        <![CDATA[
            <ul>
                <li><strong>Environments:</strong> Mac, Linux, Windows. Half way decent as a general admin; I can build out pretty much any box as a general web/application server, troubleshoot basic security and permissions, etc. </li>
                <li><strong>Data:</strong> various databases and data stores, e.g. MySQL, SQL Server, GAE Datastore, etc. I'm not a DBA at all, but I do know my way around general DB work. </li>
                <li><strong>Cloud:</strong> work frequently with EC2 and Google App Engine.</li>
                <li><strong>Documentation:</strong> Wireframes, general class and data modeling, primarily use OmniGraffle these days. </li>
                <li><strong>Management:</strong> experience managing small, agile teams through project milestones, project plan creation and tracking, etc. SVN, Mantis, Bugzilla, Campfire, Active Collab, etc. </li>
            </ul>
        ]]>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph position="r3c1">
        Update this info yo
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph position="r3c2">
        Best to update this info too
    </paragraph>
</root>